question_data = [{"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "DHCP stands for Dynamic Host Configuration Port.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "&quot;Cube&quot;, &quot;Cube 2: Hypercube&quot; and &quot;Cube Zero&quot; were directed by the same person.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                                    "question": "The Battle of Trafalgar took place on October 23rd, 1805",
                                                    "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "Druid is a mage class in &quot;Log Horizon&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "Pete Townshend&#039;s solo album, &quot;White City: A Novel&quot;, is set in the metropolitan area of Chicago.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing &quot;Spoons&quot; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "The character Plum from &quot;No Game No Life&quot; is a girl.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "The video game &quot;Fuel&quot; has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "Only one country in the world starts with the letter Q.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "YouTube personality Jenna Marbles served as an executive producer of the film Maximum Ride (2016).",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "In The Witcher 3, the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Man&#039;s Tree.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
